

## **Profile**

Hello, my name is Mikhail, I'm **20** years old **Computer science student in NSU** who is interested in creating web applications.

I have about **2 years experience** in which I managed to work on **2 commercial projects** and over 10 demo projects.

At first I was practicing as a **Python Full-stack developer** and now decided to choose a narrower focus.

# **Employment History**

#### React Front-end developer, Integral Commodities CA

NOVEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

#### About project:

Commercial web site for exporters company of Polymers, Fertilisers & Sulphur. The task was to realize the interface for a convenient search for goods and prices for further ordering,

#### My role:

- Realizing offer ordering forms
- Interactive maps with goods prices
- Basic adaptive layout
- Goods cards with documents, photos and additional information
- · Search, filtering search

#### Technologies:

- Next.js
- Google Maps Api
- Bootstrap 5
- BitBucket
- Docker / Jenkins CI

#### Links:

Web site

<u>GitHub</u>

#### Python Full-stack developer, Institute of Biology

MARCH 2020 - PRESENT

## About project:

Site for the Novosibirsk Institute of Biology. The task was to create a service for many users with functionality of creating, editing, validating and analysis researches and experiments.

### My role:

The tasks during the implementation included everything: from visualization to creating models and deploying to the server.

The work took place in a team, some of my exclusively tasks were:

• Advanced experiments analytic on the front end

## **Details**

Novosibirsk Russia +7 (913) 460-01-84 kobtsev.info@gmail.com

## Links

Portfolio Site

**GitHub** 

### Skills

HTML & CSS

**JavaScript** 

React

SCSS / SASS

Typescript

Redux

Git

Python / Django

- Authentication system & profile
- Files upload & download
- Experiments cards, search and sandbox
- Editing pages

## Technologies:

- Python / Django
- Bootstrap 4
- Javascript (ES6)
- Plotly.js
- Git
- Gunicorn / Nginx

#### Links:

Web site

# **Education**

Bachelor's Degree, Novosibirsk State University

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

Secondary education, Lyceum 130, Novosibirsk

SEPTEMBER 2008 - JUNE 2019

# **Courses**

Full-stack Python developer, Skill-factory

FEBRUARY 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021